Contact

Manga Mandi, Lahore 03086785019 (Mobile) waqar.yaqub.pk@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/waqaryaqub-7aa0ba227 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript

React.is

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Waqar Yaqub

Software Engineer at Pikessoft and Keyki | Full Stack JavaScript Developer | React | React Native | JavaScript | TypeScript | Node | Nest Js

Lahore

Summary

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Databases, JavaScript, React.js, React Native, and Object-Oriented Programming (OOP). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor in Information Technology focused in Computer/Information Technology Administration and Management from University of the Punjab.

Experience

Pikes Soft Software Engineer December 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months) Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

KEYKi

Software Engineer
December 2020 - Present (1 year 7 months)
Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

Education

University of the Punjab

Bachelor in Information Technology , Computer/Information Technology Administration and Management · (April 2016 - December 2020)